QURATU AINI

+62 812 2895 4608 | quratuaini02@gmail.com | Pekalongan, Jawa Tengah

LinkedIn | GitHub

ABOUT ME

I graduated from Dian Nuswantoro University majoring in Informatics Engineering. I am a highly motivated data enthusiast. My love for data started during my final year of college, where I did my final project on data. I am excited to bring my technical and analytical skills to the field of data analyst. With my background and experience, I believe I can make a meaningful contribution to the company and grow with the company.

EDUCATION

Dian Nuswantoro University (2019 – 2023)

Bachelor of Computer - GPA 3,81

- Understand the Basics of Programming, Basic Website Programming, Databases and Machine Learning.
- Bachelor Thesis Title: Poem Genre Classification using Support Vector Machine (SVM).

EXPERIENCE

Kampus Mengajar Angkatan 2 (August 2021 – December 2021) Teacher of SD N Gumelem Petungkriyono

- Conduct teaching activities for elementary school children in 3T areas (Disadvantaged, Frontier, Outermost).
- Assist with school administration.
- Help adapted to technology.

Bangkit (February 2022 – July 2022) Machine Learning Path

- Learn more about the field of Machine Learning.
- Applying the learning results into a program.

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Programming (Python Basic, SQL Intermediate)
- Data Visualization (Tableau Basic)
- Personal Skills (Communication, Cooperate, Responsible, Discipline)
- Languages (Indonesia Fluent, English Basic)

CERTIFICATION

- English Course by Brilliant English Course (October 2023)
- Certification Scheme of Associate Data Scientist by BNSP (March 2023)
- Certification of Bangkit Program by Kemendikbudristek (July 2022)
- TensorFlow Developer Certificate by TensorFlow (June 2022)
- Certification of Teaching Campus Program by Kemendikbudristek (February 2021)